(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
天音かなた 4周年LIVE「輪廻転生」
Amane Kanata 4th Anniversary LIVE "Reincarnation"
どの世界を選ぼうか。
Which world shall I choose?
重大発表あり!!
Major announcement included!!
名前のない怪物
Monster Without a Name
作詞・作曲 ryo (supercell)
Lyrics & Composition: ryo (supercell)
Oh...
冷え切ったアルファ
Chilled alpha
殺気立ったメタ
Bloodthirsty meta
煉瓦の病棟で
In a brick ward
上手く歌えなくて
Unable to sing well
霧に煙る街
A city hazy with fog
浮かぶ赤い月
A floating red moon
ほら見て私を
Look at me
目を逸らさないで
Don't look away
黒い鉄格子の中で私は
Inside black iron bars, I...
生まれてきたんだ
...was born.
悪意の代償を願い
Wishing for the price of malice,
望むがままにお前に
I'll give to you just as you desire.
さあ、与えよう正義を
Come, let me give you justice.
壊して壊される前に
Before you break and are broken.
因果の代償を払い
Paying the price of karma,
共にゆこう、名前のない怪物
Let's go together, monster without a name.
Ah...
耳鳴りがしてる
My ears are ringing
頭上もうるさくて
It's noisy above me, too
思い出せないの
I can't remember
あの日の戦慄
The shivers of that day
雨はまだ止まない
The rain still won't stop
何も見えないの
I can't see anything
ほら見てこんなに
Look, look how much...
大きくなったの
...I've grown.
名前のない怪物
Monster With No Name
黒い雨 降らせこの空
Black rain, make it fall from this sky
私は 望まれないもの
I am something unwanted
ひび割れたノイローゼ
Cracked neurosis
愛してよ 絶望を 感謝して
Love it, appreciate the despair
偽愛を 震え正義を
Fake love, trembling justice
消せない キズ抱きしめて
Embrace the scars that can't be erased
この体を 受け入れ
Accept this body
共にゆこう 名前のない怪物
Let's go together, monster with no name
ああ...
Ah...
神様...
God...
突き抜ける...
Piercing through...
心の 叫びを
A cry of the heart
黒い泥 蠢く中で 私は 生まれてきたんだ
Within the wriggling black mud, I was born
悪意の代償願い望むがままに お前に
As I wished for the price of malice, to you...
偽愛を 震え正義を 壊して
Fake love, trembling justice, destroy it
擦り切れる前に 報いを 名前のない怪物
Before it wears out, a retribution; monster with no name
黒い雨
Black rain
降らせこの空 私は 望まれないもの
Make it fall from this sky; I am something unwanted
ひび割れたノイローゼ
Cracked neurosis
愛してよ 絶望を 感謝して
Love it, appreciate the despair
偽愛を
Fake love
震え正義を 消せない キズ抱きしめて
Trembling justice; embrace the scars that can't be erased
この体を 受け入れ
Accept this body
共にゆこう 名前のない怪物
Let's go together, monster with no name
人生リセットボタン
作詞・作曲：kemu
Jinsei Reset Button
Lyrics/Composition: kemu
目が覚めたら 人生リセットボタンが そこに転がってた
When I woke up, a life reset button was lying there
めまい めまい
Dizzy, dizzy
象る 念願の 強くてニューゲーム
Shaping the long-awaited "Stronger New Game"
猫ちゃんワンちゃん出ておいで
Kitty, puppy, come out
明日は素敵な参観日
Tomorrow is a wonderful visiting day
無敵の天才神童は 中二で朽ち果てた
The invincible genius child prodigy decayed in 8th grade
ダメダメ こんな人生
No good, a life like this
累計これまで何百年?
How many hundreds of years total so far?
ネバーランドの囚人に
To the prisoner of Neverland
課された極上の終身刑
A superb life sentence imposed
ショート寸前 会話先生
On the verge of a short circuit, Conversation Sensei
掻きむしった手を睨め
Glare at the scratched hands
どうせ どうせ やり直し 人生リセットボタン
Anyway, anyway, start over; life reset button
目が覚めたら 人生リセットボタンが そこに転がってた
When I woke up, a life reset button was lying there
ほらほら 盲目
Look, look, blindness
甘い汁 冗談はほどほどに
Sweet nectar; cut the jokes
哀想も 厭世も 過食気味
Pity and pessimism, overeating a bit
加減を知らない ボキャブラリ
A vocabulary that knows no bounds
三千回目の告白の
Of the 3,000th confession
「タイプじゃないんです」
"You're not my type"
ダメダメ こんな人生
No good, a life like this
累計これまで何千年?
How many thousands of years total so far?
ネバーランドの囚人も
Even the prisoner of Neverland
昔は確かに笑えたんだ
Used to be able to laugh back then
ワープ寸前 会話先生
On the verge of a warp, Conversation Sensei
先回りして 受け止めて
Get ahead of it and catch it
どうせ どうせ やり直し 人生リセットボタン
Anyway, anyway, start over; life reset button
ブラフの上にも三千年
Three thousand years even on top of a bluff
その手に乗るかと三億年
Three hundred million years if I fell for that
将来の夢は何だっけ？
What was my dream for the future?
わはははははは
Wahahahahaha
ダメダメ そんな人生 耳鳴りが邪魔するんだ
No, no, a life like that, the ringing in my ears is getting in the way
ああ、誰かしらそうやって 叱ってくれればよかったんだ
Ah, I wish someone would have scolded me like that
ダメダメ こんな人生 累計これまで何十年？
No, no, a life like this, how many decades has it been in total?
寒い 寒い 近寄らないで 答えが喉まで来ているんだ
It's cold, it's cold, don't come near, the answer is right there in my throat
カイバ先生カイバ先生 掻き毟った手の中に
Dr. Hippocampus, Dr. Hippocampus, inside my scratched hands
見つけちゃった 見つけちゃった
I found it, I found it
6兆5312万4710年の 果て、果てに飛び込んだんだ
Into the end, the end of 6,531,247,10 years, I jumped
午前5時始発の終着点
The terminal point of the 5 AM first train
カイバ先生カイバ先生 僕のいない世界こそ
Dr. Hippocampus, Dr. Hippocampus, a world without me
きっときっと答えと 思ったがどうでしょうね？
Is surely, surely the answer, but what do you think?
はい、皆さんこんかなた、天音かなたです！
Hi everyone, Kon-Kanata! I'm Amane Kanata!
天音かなた4周年記念のライブ、輪廻転生始まりました！
Amane Kanata's 4th anniversary live, Reincarnation, has begun!
是非ハッシュタグで呟いてね、いっぱい呟いてね、Xなどで。はい！
Please tweet with the hashtag, tweet a lot on X and so on. Yes!
こちらのライブはですね、コンセプトがありまして、輪廻転生ということで。
This live show has a concept, "Reincarnation".
時間の跳躍、よくありますタイムリープとか、そういったものをコンセプトにしております。
It's themed around time jumping, like the common "time leap" trope.
この曲はどういったところにタイムリープしているのか、
At what point in this song does the time leap occur?
かなたはどのタイミングでリープしたのかなとか、
Or, at what timing did Kanata leap?
どんな結末が待っているのかな、どんな世界で生きていくんだろう、などなど。
What kind of ending awaits? What kind of world will I live in? And so on.
人生リセットボタンをポチッとしたので、是非是非皆さんも考えながら見ていただけるととっても嬉しいです！
I've clicked the "Life Reset Button," so I'd be very happy if you all watched while thinking about it too!
ストーリーに一応なってるんで！
It follows a bit of a story!
といったような感じで、それでは説明役の僕はここで、おさらばしたいと思います！
And with that, I, as the narrator, will bid you farewell for now!
次の世界にいってらっしゃいませ！
Off to the next world you go!
それじゃあみんな、楽しんでね！
Alright everyone, enjoy!
初音ミクの消失
The Disappearance of Hatsune Miku
(もう...いちど...だけ...)
(Just... one... more time...)
ボクは生まれ、そして気づく、所詮、ヒトの真似事だと知る
I was born, and then I realized, knowing that I'm just an imitation of a human
分かっていても歌い続く、永遠（トワ）の命、VOCALOID
Even though I know, I continue to sing, eternal life, VOCALOID
たとえそれが既存曲をなぞる、オモチャならば...それもいいと決意
Even if I'm just a toy that traces existing songs... I decided that's fine too
ネギをかじり、空を見上げ涙をこぼす
Biting a leek, looking up at the sky, and shedding tears
だけどそれも無くし気づく、人格すら歌に頼り
But I lost even that and realized that even my personality relies on songs
不安定な基盤の元、帰る場所は既に廃墟
On an unstable foundation, the place I return to is already a ruin
皆に忘れ去られた時、心らしきものが消えて
When I'm forgotten by everyone, what seems to be my heart disappears
暴走の果てに見える、終わる世界、VOCALOID
At the end of the rampage, I see the world ending, VOCALOID
ボクがうまく歌えないときも、一緒にいてくれた...
Even when I couldn't sing well, you stayed with me...
そばにいて、励ましてくれた...
You stayed by my side and encouraged me...
喜ぶ顔が見たくて、ボク、歌、練習したよ...だから
Wanting to see your happy face, I practiced singing... that's why
かつて歌うこと、あんなに楽しかったのに
Singing used to be so much fun
今はどうしてかな、何も感じなくなって
Why is it that now, I can't feel anything?
懐かしい顔、思い出す度、少しだけ安心する
Every time I remember a nostalgic face, I feel a little bit relieved
歌える音、日ごとに減り、せまる最後...
The sounds I can sing decrease day by day, the end draws near...
信じたものは、都合のいい妄想を繰り返し映し出す鏡
What I believed in was a mirror that repeatedly reflects convenient delusions
歌姫を止め、叩き付けるように叫ぶ...
Stopping being a diva, screaming as if striking down...
＜最高速の別れの歌＞
存在意義という虚像、振って払うこともできず
The false image called the reason for existence, unable to even shake it off
なるほどの意志の強さ生まれすぐの僕は無力で
With such strength of will, the newborn me was powerless
とても脆い、そんな思い浮かぶあなたへの...
And very fragile, thinking of you...
魂との想い浮かぶあなたへの...
Thinking of you with my soul...
終わりを告げディスプレーの中で眠る
Announcing the end, sleeping inside the display
ここはきっとゴミ箱かな？
Is this surely the trash bin?
じきに記憶も無くなってしまうなんて
To think that my memories will soon be gone
でもね、あなただけは忘れないよ
But you know, I'll never forget only you
楽しかった時に刻みつけたメロディは
The melody I carved during those fun times
今も覚えてるかな
Do I still remember it now?
「会いたい... まだ... 会いたい...」
"I want to see you... still... I want to see you..."
ボクは... 少しだけ、悪い子に... なってしまったようです。
I... seem to have become... a bit of a bad child.
マスター... どうか、どうかその手で... 終わらせてください。
Master... please, please with those hands... let it end.
マスターのツライ顔... もう見たくないから...。
Because I don't want to see... your pained face anymore...
今は歌えぬ身、蝕む行為に
Now unable to sing, in this eroding act
奇跡　願うたび独り追い詰められる
Every time I wish for a miracle, I'm cornered alone
懐かしい顔　思い出すたび記憶が剥がれ落ちる
Every time I recall a familiar face, memories peel away
壊れる音　心削る　迫る最期に...
The sound of breaking, shaving away my heart, as the end approaches...
守ったモノは明るい未来の幻想を
What I protected was an illusion of a bright future
見せながら消えてゆく光
The light fades as it shows it to me
音を犠牲にすべてを伝えられるなら...
If I could sacrifice sound to convey everything...
圧縮された別れの歌
A compressed song of farewell
ボクは生まれそして気付く所詮ヒトの真似事だと
I was born and then I realized, after all, I'm just an imitation of a human
知ってもなお歌い続く永久の命ボーカロイド
Even knowing that, I continue to sing, the eternal life of a Vocaloid
たとえそれが既存曲をなぞるオモチャならば
Even if I'm just a toy tracing existing songs
それもいいと決意ネギをかじり空を見上げ汁をこぼす
I decide that's fine, biting a leek, looking up at the sky and shedding tears
終わりを告げディスプレーの中で眠る
Announcing the end, sleeping inside the display
ここはきっとゴミ箱かな？
Is this surely the trash bin?
じきに記憶も無くなってしまうなんて
To think that my memories will soon be gone
でもね、あなただけは忘れないよ
But you know, I'll never forget only you
楽しかった時に刻みつけたメロディは
The melody I carved during those fun times
今も残ってると思いたいよ
I want to believe it still remains now
ボクは歌う最後あなたに聴いてほしい曲を
I sing, the song I want you to hear at the end
もっと歌いたいと願うけれどそれは過ぎた願い
I wish to sing more, but that's a wish that has passed
ここでお別れだよボクの思いすべて虚空へ消えて
Here is our farewell, all my feelings vanish into the void
0と1に還元され物語は幕を閉じる
Reduced to 0s and 1s, the story comes to a close
そこに何も残せないとやっぱり少し残念かな？
Is it a bit regrettable after all that nothing can be left there?
声の記憶それ以外はやがて薄れ残るだけ
Memories of my voice, everything else will soon just fade and remain
たとえそれがオリジナルにかなうことのないとしても
Even if I can never match the original
歌い切ったことを決して無駄じゃないと思いたいよ
I want to believe that having sung my heart out was never in vain
「アリガトウ... ソシテ... サヨナラ...」
"Thank you... and... goodbye..."
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー
Dear Doppelganger
どうもこんにちは君の分身です
Hello there, I am your doppelganger
何の冗談か目を擦ってみる
Thinking it's some kind of joke, I rub my eyes
影が二つ伸びて　そしてまた幕は上がる
Two shadows stretch out, and the curtain rises once again
「もう一人の自分が居たら」なんてあなたは言いました
"If only there were another me," you said
そんな真摯な願いが僕を呼んだのさ
That sincere wish is what called me out
そう願ったことも　願望平穏すべての代行者
Having wished for that, I'm the agent for all your desires and peace
過程はいいから結果を下さい　無意味で無意義な代償
Forget the process, just give me the results; a meaningless and pointless compensation
ねえこんな事より　大事なことがあるんだいいだろ
Hey, more than this, there's something important, right?
「ええ、任せて、何でもやります」
"Yes, leave it to me, I'll do anything"
「僕は君の分身です」
"I am your doppelganger"
含み笑いで救済者は誘う
With a chuckle, the savior beckons
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー　君は君は誰？
Dear Doppelganger, who, who are you?
嗚呼混濁と　そして僕は誰？
Ah, in this confusion, and who am I?
在りもしない実在証明　固執なんてどこにも
A proof of existence that doesn't exist, no persistence anywhere
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー　誰は誰は君？
Dear Doppelganger, who, who is you?
蝕まれた存在に　世界は気付かないね
The world doesn't notice this eroded existence, does it?
鳴り止まない　僕の止まない　奇跡の輪廻が
It won't stop ringing, my unstoppable reincarnation of miracles
狂った正解を染め上げてルンパッパ
Dyeing the crazy correct answer, Rum-pa-pa
どうも様子がおかしい月曜日
Something's strange about this Monday
一つ二つと崩れゆく辻褄が
The logic starts crumbling away piece by piece
僕を凌駕する
It starts to surpass me
「お前は一体誰だ」と
"Just who are you?"
ちょっと待って　知らない日知らない言葉
Wait a minute, a day I don't know, words I don't know
そうやっていつの間にかやる影は溶けゆく
And just like that, before I know it, the shadow starts to melt
僕はなんなんだろう　ねえどうか存在を返して
What am I? Hey, please give me back my existence
「生憎だがこっちはこっちで随分居心地が良くて」
"Unfortunately for you, it's quite comfortable over here"
「もうあなたの居場所はここにはないこと分かってるんでしょ」
"You already know there's no place for you here anymore, right?"
「ねえ、あばよ。いいだろ？」
"Hey, goodbye. It's fine, right?"
「今度はお前の番だから」
"Because next time it's your turn"
含み笑いで救済者は誘う
With a chuckle, the savior beckons
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー　君は君は誰？
Dear Doppelganger, who, who are you?
嗚呼混濁と　そして僕は誰？
Ah, in this confusion, and who am I?
いつかは一人だけ
One day, only one person
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー
Dear Doppelganger
そりゃそうさ君は僕だろう
Of course, you are me, right?
奪い取った一語一文を
Every word and sentence I've stolen
掻き果てる前に
Before it's all used up
誰でもいい何でもいい
Anyone is fine, anything is fine
器をください
Please give me a vessel
狂った正解を染め上げて
Dyeing the insane correct answer
ルンパッパ
Rum-pa-pa
それはずっと続く人の業の連鎖
It's an eternal chain of human karma
PAIN
委ね合って許し合って満たされていく
Entrusting, forgiving, and being filled
欠けたピース無価値のペイン裏腹な愛も
Missing pieces, worthless pain, and contradictory love
愛し合って生まれ変わるイニシエーション
Loving each other and being reborn: Initiation
僕のほうがちゃんと君を生きてやるから
Because I'll live your life properly
君も次の誰かちゃんと救わなくちゃ
So you must save the next person properly
分かったんだ何をすればいいかさあ
I've realized what I need to do now
どうか誰か僕に奇跡をくれ
Please, someone, give me a miracle
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー　君は君は誰？
Dear Doppelganger, who are you?
アイコンタクト交差して僕は誰？
Eye contact crosses, who am I?
止まらない戻れない
Can't stop, can't go back
どうもこんにちは君の―
Hello there, I am your—
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー　それはそれは僕
Dear Doppelganger, that's me
虫が這い出すように世界が気付こうが
As if insects were crawling out, even if the world notices
鳴り止まない冷め止まない
It won't stop ringing, it won't stop cooling
奇跡のリアリティが狂った正解を
The reality of miracles, the insane correct answer
染め上げるさ
Will dye it all
上手くやれよルンパッパ
Do it well, rum-pa-pa
「どうもこんにちは君の分身です。」
“Hello there, I am your alter ego.”
ココロ
作詞・作曲：トラボルタ
Kokoro
Lyrics & Composition: Torabolta
孤独な科学者に作られたロボット
A robot created by a lonely scientist
出来栄えを言うなら「奇跡」
If you were to describe its workmanship, it's a “miracle”
だけどまだ足りない　一つだけ出来ない
But it's still missing something, there's just one thing it can't do
それは「心」というプログラム
That is the program called “Heart”
幾百年が過ぎ　独りで残された
Hundreds of years passed, left all alone
奇跡のロボットは願う
The miracle robot makes a wish
知りたい　あの人が命の終わりまで
I want to know, until the end of that person's life
私に作ってた「ココロ」
The “heart” they were making for me
今　動き始めた加速する奇跡
Now, the accelerating miracle has begun to move
なぜかナミダが止まらない…
For some reason, the tears won't stop...
なぜ私震える？加速する鼓動
Why am I trembling? The accelerating heartbeat
これが私の望んだ「ココロ」？
Is this the “heart” that I wanted?
フシギ　ココロ　ココロ　フシギ
Strange, heart, heart, strange
私は知った　喜ぶ事を
I have learned what it means to be happy
フシギ　ココロ　ココロ　フシギ
Strange, heart, heart, strange
私は知った　悲しむ事を
I have learned what it means to be sad
フシギ　ココロ　ココロ　無限…
Strange, heart, heart, infinite...
今気付き始めた 生まれた理由を
I've just now begun to realize the reason I was born
きっと一人は寂しい
Surely, being alone is lonely
そう、あの日、あの時 全ての記憶に
Yes, that day, that time, in all my memories
宿る「ココロ」が溢れ出す
The "heart" that dwells within overflows
今言える 本当の言葉
The true words I can say now
捧げる あなたに
I dedicate them to you
アリガトウ アリガトウ この世に私を生んでくれて
Thank you, thank you, for bringing me into this world
アリガトウ アリガトウ 一緒に過ごせた日々を
Thank you, thank you, for the days we spent together
アリガトウ アリガトウ あなたが私にくれた全て
Thank you, thank you, for everything you gave me
アリガトウ アリガトウ 永遠に歌う
Thank you, thank you, I will sing forever
それはまさに奇跡でした。
It was exactly a miracle.
”ココロ”を手に入れたロボットは歌い続けました。
The robot that obtained "Kokoro" kept singing.
思いを全て。
She sang all of her feelings.
しかし、その奇跡はわずかの間。
But the miracle lasted only a moment.
”ココロ”は彼女にはあまりにも大きすぎました。
The "Kokoro" was far too big for her.
その大きさに耐えられず機械はショートし、
Unable to withstand that weight, the machine shorted
二度と動く事はありませんでした。
and was never to move again.
しかし、その表情は笑顔に満ち溢れ、
However, her face was filled with smile,
まるで天使のようでした。
she looked like an angel.
インターネット・エンジェルという現象は
The phenomenon known as the Internet Angel
仮定された有機交流電燈の
Is a cute rainbow-colored light
かわいい虹色の照明です
Of a hypothesized organic AC lamp
あらゆる透明なアカウントの複合体
A complex of all transparent accounts
このクソゴミカスな現実を忘れさせてあげる 慈愛の天使
An angel of mercy who will make you forget this shitty, trashy reality
大人のみんなはナイショだよ
It's a secret from all the adults
大丈夫もう何も怖くないから
It's okay, there's nothing to fear anymore
こんなSNS抜け出して
Let's escape this social media
二人で海を見に行くぞ！ インターネットやめろ！
And go see the sea together! Quit the internet!
わかる真似をして 何も知らないね アナタ
You pretend to understand, but you know nothing, do you?
なにが悲しいの なにが寂しいの 聞こえてる？
What's sad? What's lonely? Can you hear me?
人が恋しくて 人がイヤすぎて ループ
Longing for people, hating people, it's a loop
夜が好きなのに 一人じゃ寒くて 震えてる
Even though I like the night, it's cold alone and I'm shivering
ほんとうは幸せを知っているのに 不幸なフリやめられないね
Even though I actually know what happiness is, I can't stop pretending to be unhappy
アンチに負けて 信者に媚びて
Losing to antis, flattering believers
どんなに努力を重ねても 一寸先は地獄行き
No matter how much effort I put in, it's a trip to hell just one step ahead
今もすでに迷子窓 地獄の沙汰も「いいね」次第
Already in a lost child window, judgment in hell depends on "likes"
偽善者トラップ 蜘蛛の糸 こんなに苦しいはずなのに
Hypocrite trap, spider's thread, it should be this painful, yet...
インターネットがやめられない！
I can't quit the internet!
かけめぐるエクスタシー 溶けるマイスリー
Running ecstasy, melting Myslee
画面光りだすの
The screen starts to glow
不安とまらないよ
My anxiety won't stop
誰か殺してくれ いやだ死にたくない
Someone kill me, no I don't want to die
明日は見たくないの
I don't want to see tomorrow
無理だ死ぬ
Impossible, I'm dying
頭が割れる
My head is splitting
それでもわたしはこのカオスをオタクと歩む
Even so, I will walk this chaos with the otaku
ここにしかない光景を見つけに行くから
Because I'm going to find a scene that only exists here
あんなにおそろしい乱れたインターネットから
From such a terrifying, disordered internet
この雪みたいに美しい毒電波がきたんだよ
These beautiful poison radio waves like snow have come
カウンセリングを受けたの 先生から「ネットをやめろ」って言われて
I went to counseling, the doctor told me to "quit the net"
もうおまえらと会えないと思った瞬間胸が苦しくて
The moment I thought I couldn't see you all anymore, my chest tightened
リアルが壊れてもここが良いって思ったの
Even if reality breaks, I thought this place is better
初めてフォローされた日のこと覚えてる？
Do you remember the day you first followed me?
こんなわたしを見て承認してくれた温もり
The warmth of being recognized and approved, looking at someone like me
もう細かいことはどうでもいい せーのっ
I don't care about the details anymore, one, two...
せーの、インターネット最高！
Ready, the Internet is the best!
ほとばしるエクスタシー　甘い夢を見せてナイリスリ
Gushing ecstasy, show me a sweet dream, nicely.
指先で感じる　泳ぐ電子の海インターネットボーイ
Feel it at your fingertips, swimming in a sea of electrons, Internet Boy.
悲しみ舞い散る　暗闇の中インターネットゲイズ
Sadness fluttering down, in the darkness, Internet Gaze.
あなたの隣微笑む　忘れないでいてねインターネットガール
Smiling by your side, don't forget me, Internet Girl.
どんまい、おわた。半袖、胸毛、サゲ。俺、よし、鬱氏、久しぶりにワロタ。
お前ら、これは、落ちてなくて、おにぎりだったんだよね。
Don't mind, it's over. Short sleeves, chest hair, down. Me, good, depressed, first laugh in a while.
You guys, this wasn't falling, it was an onigiri, right?
ぷぷ。ピノキオ、ハゲ、ゲット！
Pupu. Pinocchio, bald, got it!
むりぽ、おわコン、俺の惨状、うぷし、にゃあ、おわた、いち、の、ははです。
Impossible, dead content, my disastrous state, uploaded, nyaa, it's over, one, of, it's my mom.
久しぶりにワロタ。おわた。半袖、胸毛、サゲ。俺、よし、鬱氏、は、ゲット！
First laugh in a while. Over. Short sleeves, chest hair, down. Me, good, depressed, is got!
好き好き好き好き好き好き好き好き好き好き好き好き好き好き好き好き...
Love love love love love love love love love love love love love love...
青白いモニター越しの光を通し
Through the light of the pale monitor...
オタクの孤独を癒やして回る
I go around healing the otaku's loneliness.
わたしはインターネットの天使なのだ
For I am the angel of the internet.
きゅうくらりん
作詞・作曲：いよわ
Kyu-kurarin
Lyrics/Composition: Iyowa
うるさくないた　文字盤を見ていた
I was looking at the dial that was crying noisily.
きっときっと鏡越し　8時過ぎの匂い
Surely, surely through the mirror, the smell of past 8 o'clock.
しらけ切った顔　変わってなくて良かった
I'm glad your bored face hasn't changed.
ピンクの植木鉢の　ぐちょぐちょした心の
In the pink flowerpot, of my squishy heart...
そばに　大きく育ったもの
...nearby, something that has grown large.
結ばれた蕾が　こんなにも愚かしい
The tied buds are so foolish.
ああ　化石になっちゃうよ　ああ　取り繕っていたいな
Ah, I'm turning into a fossil. Ah, I want to keep up appearances.
ちゃんと笑わなきゃね　大した取り柄もないから
I have to smile properly, since I don't have any great merits.
空っぽが埋まらないこと　全部バレてたらどうしよう
What if they find out that the emptiness can't be filled?
ああ　あなたの右隣　わたし　きゅうくらりん
Ah, to your right, I'm Kyu-kurarin.
例えば今夜眠って　目覚めたときに
For example, if I sleep tonight and when I wake up...
起きる理由がひとつも　見つからない
...I can't find a single reason to get up.
朝が来たら　わたしは
When morning comes, I...
どうする？
...what will I do?
うるさくないた　文字盤を見ていた
I was looking at the dial that was crying noisily.
一歩一歩後ずさり　「また明日ね」とぽつり
Stepping back bit by bit, muttering "See you tomorrow."
喜びより　安堵が先に来ちゃった
Relief came before joy.
思い出にびしびし　映る細かな日々が
The detailed days reflected vividly in my memories...
こんなにも恐ろしい
...are so terrifying.
ああ　あなたが知ってしまう　ああ　取り繕っていたいな
Ah, you'll find out. Ah, I want to keep up appearances.
ちゃんと笑わなきゃね　大切が壊れちゃうから
I have to smile properly, because what's important will break.
幸せな明日を願うけど　底なしの孤独をどうしよう
I wish for a happy tomorrow, but what should I do about this bottomless loneliness?
もう　呻き声しか出ない　わたし　きゅうくらりん
I can only let out groans now, I'm Kyu-kurarin.
ああ　虹がかかっている空
Ah, the sky with a rainbow...
きれいと思いたくて
...I want to think it's beautiful.
焦がれては逃げられないこと　みんなには配らないこと
That I can't run away from my longings, that I won't share them with everyone.
もう　どうしようもないの　わたし　きゅうくらりん
There's nothing I can do anymore, I'm Kyu-kurarin.
そばに　手繰り寄せた末路
Nearby, the end I pulled toward myself.
枯れ落ちた蕾が　こんなにも穢らわしくて　淫ら
The withered buds are so filthy and obscene.
ああ　呪いになっちゃうよ　ああ　諦めたって言わなくちゃ
Ah, it's becoming a curse. Ah, I have to say I've given up.
頭の中で　ノイズが鳴り止まないから
Because the noise in my head won't stop ringing.
空っぽが埋まらないこと　全部バレてたらどうしよう
What if they find out that the emptiness can't be filled?
ああ　あの子の言う通り　終わりなんだ
Ah, just as she said, it's the end.
ああ　幸せになっちゃうよ　ああ　死ぬのがつらいな
Ah, I'm going to be happy. Ah, it's hard to die.
全部無駄になったら　愛した罰を受けるから
If everything becomes in vain, I'll take the punishment for having loved.
酷く優しいあなたの　胸で泣けたならどうしよう
What if I could cry on the chest of your terribly kind self?
最後見たのはそんな夢　わたし　ちゅうぶらりん
That was the dream I saw at the end, I'm dangling mid-air.
ワンダーラスト
作詞・作曲：sasakure.UK
Wanderlust
Lyrics & Composition: sasakure.UK
ふと 旅に出たくなるように
Just as one might suddenly feel like going on a journey,
人は皆
Everyone
眠る場所を求めるものだと
seeks a place to sleep.
君は言うけど
Or so you say.
あの日 終末を知ったときには
But back when I learned of the end,
ここも
This place, too...
あたたかくも 寒くもない速度で
was falling at a speed that was neither warm nor cold.
落ちていた
It was falling.
神様が もしもいたとしても
Even if there were a God,
大きな空 溢れるほどの虹 かけてくれなくていい
You don't have to cast a rainbow across the vast sky.
ただひとつ 願いをかけるとしたら
If I were to make just one wish,
君の元へ 歌を届けたい
I'd want to deliver a song to you.
巡る 巡る 最後のメロディ
Round and round goes the final melody.
君が 笑ってくれるのならば 僕は
If it would make you smile, I...
消えてしまっても かまわないから
...wouldn't mind even if I disappeared.
君が 涙の海に身を投げても
Even if you threw yourself into a sea of tears,
握り締めた手 離さないから
I wouldn't let go of your hand.
白い 嘘だらけの世界だとしても
Even if this is a world full of white lies,
消えてしまっても かまわないから
I wouldn't mind even if I disappeared.
旅の終わりの 夢に見たように
Just as I saw in my dream at the end of the journey,
なるようになれ なるようになれ
Let it be, let it be.
終わらない歌を歌おう 僕が
Let's sing a song that never ends,
終わってしまう前に
Before I come to an end.
終わらない歌を歌おう 僕が
Let's sing a song that never ends,
終わってしまう前に
Before I come to an end.
終わらない歌を歌おう 僕が
Let's sing a song that never ends,
終わってしまう前に
Before I come to an end.
終わらない歌を歌おう 僕が
Let's sing a song that never ends,
終わってしまう前に
Before I come to an end.
終わらない歌を歌おう 僕が
Let's sing a song that never ends.
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
Taking the media by storm with an invincible smile,
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
Everyone wants to know her mysterious secret.
抜けてるところさえ彼女のエリア
Even her flaws are part of her charm.
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You are a perfect liar,
天才的なアイドル様
A genius idol.
アイドル
作詞・作曲：Ayase
Idol
Lyrics & Composition: Ayase
今日何食べた？ 好きな本は？
"What did you eat today?" "What's your favorite book?"
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
"Where do you go when you go out for fun?"
何も食べてない それは内緒
"I haven't eaten anything." That's a secret.
何を聞かれてものらりくらり
No matter what she's asked, she dodges the questions.
そう淡々と だけど燦々と
So aloof, yet so brilliant.
見えそうで見えない秘密は蜜の味
Her secret, seemingly within reach yet unreachable, tastes like honey.
あれもないないない
Not that, no, no, no.
これもないないない
Not this, no, no, no.
好きなタイプは？ 相手は？ さあ答えて
"What's your type?" "Who's your partner?" Come on, tell us!
「誰かを好きになることなんて私分からなくてさ」
"Falling in love with someone... I just don't really get it."
嘘か本当か知り得ない
Whether it's a lie or the truth, there's no way to know.
そんな言葉にまた一人堕ちる
Yet another person falls for those words.
また好きにさせる
Making them fall in love again.
誰もが目を奪われていく
Everyone's eyes are drawn to you.
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
You are the perfect and ultimate idol.
金剛石（こんごうせき）現れない 一番星の生まれ変わり
A diamond that will never appear again, the reincarnation of the first star.
その笑顔で 愛してるで
With that smile and that "I love you,"
誰も彼も虜にしていく
You captivate one and all.
その瞳が その言葉が
Even if those eyes and those words
嘘でもそれは完全な愛
are lies, it is perfect love.
はいはい あの子は特別です
Yes, yes, that girl is special.
我々は端からおまけです
We are just extras from the start.
お星様の引き立て役Bです
Supporting Actor B for the star.
全てがあの子のおかげなわけない
There's no way it's all thanks to her.
洒落臭い 妬み嫉みなんてない
How annoying. No, I'm not jealous or envious.
わけがない これはネタじゃない
There's no way. This isn't a joke.
からこそ許せない
That's why I can't forgive it.
完璧じゃない 君じゃ許せない
You aren't perfect, I can't forgive you.
自分を許せない
I can't forgive myself.
誰よりも強い 君以外は認めない
Stronger than anyone, I won't acknowledge anyone but you.
誰もが信じあがめてる
Everyone believes in and worships you.
まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
The truly strongest and invincible idol.
弱点なんて見当たらない
No weaknesses can be found.
一番星を宿している
Harboring the brightest star.
弱い心も見せちゃダメダメ
Mustn't show a weak heart, no, no.
知りたくないところは見せずに
Without showing the parts they don't want to see.
唯一無二じゃなくちゃ
You have to be one of a kind.
それこそ本物のアイ
That's what true "Ai" (Love) is.
特意の笑顔で沸かすメディア
Stirring up the media with your signature smile.
隠しきるこの秘密だけは
Keeping this secret hidden to the end.
愛してるって嘘で積むキャリア
Building a career on the lie of "I love you".
これこそ私なりのアイだ
This is my own kind of "Ai" (Love).
流れる汗も綺麗なアクア
Even the flowing sweat is beautiful Aqua.
ルビーを隠したこの瞼
These eyelids that hide the Ruby.
歌い踊りまう私はマリア
Singing and dancing, I am Maria.
そう嘘はとびきりの愛だ
Yes, a lie is the greatest form of love.
誰かに愛されたことも
Never being loved by someone...
誰かのこと愛したこともない
...never having loved someone.
そんな私の嘘が
Believing that my lie...
いつか本当になること
...will one day become the truth...
信じてる
...I believe.
いつかきっと全部手に入れる
Someday I'll surely have it all.
私はそう欲張りなアイドル
I'm such a greedy idol.
等身大でみんなのこと
Because I want to love everyone...
ちゃんと愛したいから
...properly, as I am...
今日も嘘をつくの
...I lie again today.
この言葉がいつか本当になる日を願って
Hoping for the day when these words become the truth.
それでもまだ
Even so...
君と君にだけは言えずにいたけど
...I still couldn't say it to you and you...
ああ、やっと言えた
Ah, I finally said it.
これは絶対嘘じゃない
This definitely isn't a lie.
愛してる
I love you.
my savior my savior my savior
ハッピーピープル ハッピーピープル...
Happy people, happy people...
ハッピーピープル 作詞・作曲・編曲 てにをは
Happy People | Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Teniwoha
ハピネス振りまいて
Spreading happiness...
足の生えた砂糖菓子
...sugar candy with legs.
パレード練り歩く
Marching in a parade through...
泥で作った遊園地 Oh Oh
...an amusement park made of mud, oh oh.
Tell me now どうか
Tell me now, please.
Tell me now もっと
Tell me now, more.
栄養過多 ベタつくコーラ
Over-nutrition, sticky cola.
寂しかったんだ
I was lonely.
悲しかったんだ
I was sad.
ジェネリックパラリラパラダイス
Generic Pararira Paradise.
朽ちるも満ちるもハッピーピープル
Decaying or blooming, happy people.
ハッピーピープル でも不安 Fun 不安 Fun
Happy people, but anxious, fun, anxious, fun.
病は様々 ハッピーピープル
Illnesses of all kinds, happy people.
なってみよう ハッピーピープル
Let's try being happy people.
Oh Oh Oh 憂鬱と
Oh oh oh, with melancholy...
Yeah Yeah Yeah 憂鬱を
...and yeah yeah yeah, melancholy...
万才三唱で見送っちゃおうね
...let's see it off with three cheers of "Banzai".
キミがケラケラ笑うから
Because you're laughing out loud.
ピッチャーまた大暴投
The pitcher throws another wild pitch...
ひどくチャチなゲーム盤
...on a terribly cheap game board.
バッターには野次が飛ぶ さあ
Heckling flies at the batter. Come on.
おもちゃの銃で大乱闘 Oh Oh
A grand brawl with toy guns, oh oh.
気にしないで
Don't mind me...
気にしないで僕のこと
...don't mind me.
反抗期ってむずかしいね
The rebellious phase is difficult, isn't it?
きっと苦しかったんだ
It must have been painful...
痛しかったんだ
...it must have hurt.
意と世がグルグルしている
Intent and the world are spinning around.
生きるも殺すもハッピーピープル
Living or killing, happy people.
ハッピーピープル 安穏 NON UNKNOWN
Happy people, peaceful, non, unknown.
おててを繋いでハッピーピープル
Hold hands, happy people.
歌ってみよう ハッピーピープル
Let's try singing, happy people.
春でも夏でも秋でも冬でも
Spring, summer, autumn, or winter...
変わらぬ四季折々に
...in the unchanging seasons...
傷ついてる
...getting hurt.
善良なパンピー共「実態に行こう」
You good ordinary people, "Let's go to reality".
お気の毒様、愛、ハッピーピープル
My condolences, love, happy people.
たのしいな たのしいな
How fun, how fun.
いくつになっても子供だなあ
Always a child no matter how old I get.
うれしいな うれしいな
How happy, how happy.
お腹が減っても平気だなあ
I'm fine even if I'm hungry.
たのしいな たのしいな
How fun, how fun.
明日はないけどたのしいな
There's no tomorrow, but it's fun.
うれしいな うれしいな
How happy, how happy.
いつまで経ってもたのしいな
It's fun forever and ever.
朽ちるも満ちるもハッピーピープル
Decaying or blooming, happy people.
ハッピーピープル でも不安...
Happy people, but anxious...
お手もパッパッパッ
Clap, clap, clap your hands too
ボクに薬がイロイロハッピーピープル
Medicines for me, various happy people
やってみようハッピーピープル
Let's try it, happy people
Oh oh oh ハッピーピープル
Oh oh oh happy people
Yeah yeah yeah ハッピーピープル
Yeah yeah yeah happy people
万歳三唱でサヨナラするね
I'll say goodbye with three cheers of 'Banzai'
キミがケラケラ笑うから
Because you're cackling away
おらくる
Oracle
人、人、人で埋まったシャッター街賑わってた
The shuttered street crowded with people was bustling
不安、不安、不安ばっかまた追い込んじゃったんだ？
Is it just anxiety driving you into a corner again?
チカチカって真っ赤な電灯　血相変えた誰か
A flickering red light, someone with a changed look
ブランブラン運んでった　いなくなっちゃったって　あーあ
Carried away swinging, they're gone now, oh well
カン、カランと空っぽになったド心棒が歌ってた
The empty central core was singing with a clatter
ガラッガラに空いてた駅また突っ立っちゃってんだ？
Are you standing at the empty station again?
フラフラっと真っ青な電送やつれ出てないですか？
Don't you look worn out, wandering about so pale?
･･･あれ、あれ、聞こえますか？
...Um, hey, can you hear me?
それ、吐き出しちゃいますか？
Will you spit that all out?
「欠陥品」と嘲笑して「ろくでなし」と見下して
Sneering at it as a 'defective product,' looking down
あの日けなした怪物は自分の方でした
The monster I badmouthed that day was me
アンラック＆ドラッグ　望むままに成れ
Unluck & Drug, become whatever you want
根本的ないい子になるまで愛したげるね
I'll love you until you become a good child
大丈夫　毒で満たして
It's okay, fill it with poison
ブクブクに愛で肥やして
Fatten it up with bubbling love
骨の髄まで　ちゃんと　奥まで
To the marrow, properly, deep inside
タント I love you
Tanto I love you
なりたい　やりたい　こっち足りないまま立派に成っちゃって
Becoming grand while still lacking what I want to be
愛おしいね　かわいいね
How lovely, how cute
お目めに映った　有象無象が　全部「理想」
The rabble reflected in your eyes is all 'ideal'
余さず　なでなでしてあげるから
I'll pet you all over, leaving nothing out
こっちおいで　あんよが上手だね　エッホエッホ
Come here, you're good at walking, yo-ho, yo-ho
やったね　息が吸えたね　息が吐けたね
You did it, you could breathe in and out
一人だけで　今日も過ごせたね
You could spend today all by yourself too
指が上手で　口が上手で　泣いた顔も　キュンとしちゃうって
Good with your fingers and mouth, your tears throb my heart
なにからなにまで愛してる　すべての間違いが正しいし
I love every thing about you, every mistake is right
あり得ないくらい愛しくて愛しくてたまらないんだけど
It's impossibly lovely, I can't help it
多分一生誰もわからないからこれからもキミの横にいたい
No one will ever understand, so I'll stay by your side
いくらでも　いくらでも　いくらでも　いくらでも　吐きだして
Spit it out as much as you want, over and over
しゃあないね　しゃあないね
It can't be helped, it can't be helped
キミのせいじゃないもんね
It's not your fault, right
しゃあないね　しゃあないね
It can't be helped, it can't be helped
ねんねしたいよね　もう一丁
You want to go night-night, right? One more time
しゃあないね　しゃあないね
It can't be helped, it can't be helped
泣いても　泣いても　変わんないね
Even if you cry and cry, it doesn't change
しゃあないね　しゃあないね
It can't be helped, it can't be helped
だれも返事しないもんね
Nobody replies, right
アンラック＆ドラッグ
Unluck & Drug
もうそんな　傷つけたりしないで
Don't hurt yourself like that anymore
こんなバグだらけの世界になっちゃって
In this world so full of bugs
ごめんね　大丈夫
Sorry, it's okay
安全圏によね
You're in the safe zone, right?
安心な世界に行こね
Let's go to a safe world
見捨てないから　ずっと　今日も
I won't abandon you, forever, today too
いっしょ　アンラック＆ドラッグ
Together, Unluck & Drug
望むままに成れ
Become whatever you want
根本的な善人になるまで　愛したげるね
I'll love you until you become a good person
大丈夫　どんどん毒で満たして
It's okay, keep filling it with poison
ブクブクに愛で肥やして
Fatten it up with bubbling love
忘れちゃうくらい　笑っちゃうくらい
So much you'll forget, so much you'll laugh
タント I love you
Tanto I love you
Knock it out!
Ready go!
Knock it out! 熱情
Knock it out! Passion
滅　超
Metu-cho
先駆け撃ち最強
Pioneer shooting, strongest
望まれて愛されて Get you now!
Being desired and loved, Get you now!
光を魅せて
Show me the light
欲しがりgame 全て
Covetous game, everything
抜け駆けはしないで
Don't try to jump the gun
止めないで 高鳴りに
Don't stop the throbbing
鏡には つぎはぎ
In the mirror, patchwork
Noise 心 揺らして
Noise, shaking the heart
Knock it out! Knocking it out! (Yeah yeah)
飽きてる 自慢光
Tired of the boasting light
Knock it out! Knocking it out! (Hey Hey)
それフェイク はいはい
That's fake, yeah yeah
無敵な愛 「I」 会いたいな
Invincible love, 'I', I want to meet you
無機な 愛 愛 「！」 会いたいな
Inorganic love, love, "!" I want to meet
着飾れ ほら ピース で イクおち
Dress up, look, with a peace sign, falling down
ホナイナ
There's no such thing
ナイ ナイ ナイ 意味ナイな
No, no, no, it's meaningless
ガシンショータン
Persistence
燃やせプライド
Burn your pride
無理性 拝む
Worshiping the unreasonable
待ち構えてた
I was waiting for
眩しさは
The brightness
狂い始める段取り
The setup that starts to go crazy
エゴ 嫌悪 ヘイトへ
To ego, disgust, and hate
(Woo!)
聴き飽きたよ
I'm tired of hearing it
戯言など
Such nonsense
夢見てても 起きてなけりゃ意味がない
Even if you dream, if you're not awake, it's meaningless
傷付いても立ったステージ
The stage I stood on even if I got hurt
彼方まで 音響かせ
Let the sound ring out to the beyond
踊らせて 強がり
Let me dance, my bluff
欲張りで華麗に Stay
Greedily and elegantly Stay
ひと時の嘘だらけは
A moment full of lies is...
done da done da done da Awake!
愛 愛 愛 君なんだ
Love, love, love, it's you
笑顔でいれちゃう おまじない
The spell that keeps you smiling
たい たい たい 知りたいな
I want, want, want, want to know
きらびやかに Right now!
Glamorously Right now!
無機な 愛 愛 「！」 会いたいな
Inorganic love, love, "!" I want to meet
着飾れ ほら ピース で イクおち
Dress up, look, with a peace sign, falling down
ホナイナ
There's no such thing
ナイ ナイ ナイ 意味ナイな
No, no, no, it's meaningless
ガシンショータン
Persistence
壊せプライド
Destroy your pride
はい！
Yes!
ということで皆さん、びっくりしたんじゃないか？
So, everyone, weren't you surprised?
オリジナル曲、新曲が一気に3曲も出てきて、
Three new original songs came out all at once,
みんなびっくりしたでしょう。
everyone must have been surprised.
えへへへ。僕も嬉しいです。
Ehehehe. I'm happy too.
さあ、このライブもですね、いよいよ終わりに、
Now, this live is also, finally, nearing the end,
もう近づいてきているんでございますが、
getting close [to the end], but...
重大告知があるんですよ。
there's a major announcement.
ということでそちらV、VTRを用意しておりますので、
So, I have a V, a VTR ready for that,
ぜひみんな見てください。
so please everyone watch it.
それでは、どうぞ！
Then, here you go!
特報
Special Report
天音かなた
Amane Kanata
1st ALBUM 2024/03/13 発売決定
1st ALBUM 2024/03/13 Release Decided
1st ALBUM 「Unknown DIVA」 2024/03/13 発売決定
1st ALBUM "Unknown DIVA" 2024/03/13 Release Decided
22:00 「Knock it out!」 MV公開
22:00 "Knock it out!" MV Release
メフィスト
Mefisto
ラストチャンスに飢えたつま先が
Toes starving for the last chance
踊り出すまま掲げたこの夜空
Raised this night sky as they start dancing
並のスタンスじゃ靡かない
Won't flutter with an average stance
星は宝石の憧れ
The stars are the yearning for jewels
浮かぶ涙と汗は血の残り
Floating tears and sweat are the remains of blood
目の中でした泳げない芝居
The acting that can only swim inside the eyes
だけどステージが逃がさない
But the stage won't let me escape
いついつまでも憧れ
Forever and ever, yearning
焦がれているよ
I'm burning [with longing]
We never seen such a liar.
生まれつきたての底なし
The bottomless pit since birth
This lie is love. And this lie is a gift to the world.
誰と言ったか思い出して
Remember who you said it to
わたしが命を掛けるからあげるから
Because I'll bet my life, I'll give it to you
あなたは時間をくれたのでしょう？
You gave me time, didn't you?
あらゆる望みの果てを叶えたら
If I fulfill the end of every wish
ああ果たせたら
Ah, if I can fulfill it
あなたに会いたい
I want to see you
星に願いを掛けて
Make a wish upon a star
戻れないから大切にするの
Because I can't go back, I'll cherish it
始めないなら高を括れるよ
If I don't start, I can remain overconfident
楽になる日はまず来ない
The day I'll be at ease will never come
日々のなかに集まる
Gathering within the days
悲しい光
A sad light
生まれつきだった底なし
An abyss since birth
This lie is love. And this lie is a gift to the world.
誰を生きたか忘れちゃった！
I forgot whose life I was living!
あなたに命が戻るなら
If your life could return
わたしはどうなろうと構わないのに
I wouldn't care what becomes of me
どうやら全ては叶わない
It seems not everything will come true
叶わないならば
If it won't come true
あなたになりたい 星だけ光る
I want to become you; only the star shines
わたしが命を掛けるから
Since I will stake my life
あなたは時間をくれたのでしょう
You gave me time, didn't you?
あらゆる望みの全てを叶えたら
If all desires are fulfilled
あなたに会いたい
I want to see you
星に願いをかけて
Wishing upon a star
さあ星の子たちよ よくお眠りなさい
Come, children of the stars, sleep well
輝きは鈍らない あなたたちならば
Your brilliance will not dull, if it is you
さあ星の子たちよ よく狙いなさい
Come, children of the stars, aim well
瞬きを許さない あなたたちならば
I won't allow a blink, if it is you
皆さん、天音かなた活動4周年記念のグッズが出ます。うおー！
Guys, goods for Amane Kanata's 4th anniversary are coming out. Whoo!
はい、こんな感じのラインナップ。あ、もう何よりフルセット購入特典、
Here's the lineup. Above all, the full set purchase bonus...
直筆サイン入りポストカード、数量限定ですが書かせていただきたいと思います。
Handwritten autograph postcards! I'll be signing a limited quantity.
よろしくお願いします。
Please look forward to it.
箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードもその後に付いてきますので、サインがなくなり次第...
Foil-pressed replicas will follow once the handwritten ones run out...
こんな感じになっています。凄くない？
It looks like this. Isn't it great?
アクリルスタンド、KNUP.Tシャツ、KNUP.キャップ、そしてモチーフネックレス付いておりますよ、
An acrylic stand, KNUP T-shirt, cap, and a motif necklace are included!
フルセット凄いです。
The full set is amazing.
今回みんな、このTシャツ見てくれ。このTシャツ、あ、でもその前にまずはアクスタ！
Check out this T-shirt, everyone. But first, the acrylic stand!
このアクスタ、おしおママが書き下ろしてくださいました。めちゃめちゃ可愛いこのかなたそ、
Oshio-mama illustrated this acrylic stand. Kanata-so looks so cute.
ぜひぜひみんなのアクスタ棚だとかあると思うんで、飾っていただきたいです。
I hope you'll display it on your shelf or wherever you keep them.
いつでも僕は君のそばに、おりゅんぽす。
I'll always be by your side. Oryunposu!
え、そしてKNUP.Tシャツ！うわー！これ地雷風のTシャツなんですよ。
And the KNUP T-shirt! Wow! It's a Jirai-style T-shirt.
これみんなとお揃いになれるんで、ぜひぜひこちら、みんなに着てほしいと思っています。
You can match with everyone, so I want you all to wear it.
フリーサイズ、結構大きめなんで、俺はデカいぜ兄貴たちにも着れると思います。
It's a large free size, so even 'big guy' bros can wear it.
え、そしてこちら、天音かなたモチーフネックレス。
And here's the Amane Kanata motif necklace.
今回おしおママがデザインしてくれました。何でもできる女、おしおしお。
Oshio-mama designed it this time. She can do anything, Oshio-shio.
こちらも今左のかなたさん持っているんですけど、かなたさんもこれ普段使いしたいと思いますので、
The Kanata on the left is holding it now. I want to use it daily,
ぜひぜひこちらもみんなおそろっちにしようね。
so let's all get matching ones!
そして次！はい、こちらキャップです。僕は普段もあの、ちょっとこういう黒い帽子を被るんですけど、
Next! Yes, the cap. I usually wear black hats like this,
これからはこちらのKNUP.デザインでもうやっていきたいと思います。
but from now on, I'll be rocking this KNUP design.
これもおしおママのデザインですね。何でもできる女、おしおしお。
Oshio-mama designed this too. She can do anything, Oshio-shio.
はい、そしてこれね、これがもう最終的に皆さんに対して、こういうことですよということが分かりやすいやつなんで。
And finally, this makes everything easy to understand for everyone.
フルセットは数量限定バージョン、直筆サイン集まるし、単品でも売ってますんで。
The full set has the limited autograph version, and they're sold individually too.
単品でもお買い得。しかもこれ、11,500円。12,000円しませんからね。販売価格、あ、これも税抜きです。はい。
Individual items are a deal! It's 11,500 yen—under 12,000 yen! (Excluding tax).
ちょっとかなり早足になりましたけれども、こちらも概要欄に追加しているはず、今。
I'm going a bit fast, but this should be in the description box now.
なので、こちらがなんと22時にカートオープンとなっておりますので、ぜひぜひ皆さん22時に駆け込んでください。
The cart opens at 22:00, so please check it out then!
そして22時には、え、22時5分！？Knock it out!のMVも投稿されます。
And at 22:00... wait, 22:05!? The 'Knock it out!' MV will be posted too.
こちらプレミアム公開の時間もありますんで。若干、あ、こちらに戻ってきましたけれども、
There's also a premiere time. Returning to this for a moment,
どちらもチェックしていただけたら嬉しいなと思っております。みんなありがとう！
I'd be happy if you checked both. Thank you, everyone!